听得见吗?
Can hear me well.
大家好,欢迎,这是辅导课
Hello everyone. Welcome. This is the tutorial session
关于
for
3D扫描仪,我在这里 纺织实验室,我们是
3D scanners, I'm here the textile lab and we're
将展示我们现有的两种技术
going to show the two technologies we have available
这里,其中一个是Kinect
here. One of them is the connect.
Kinect实际上是从Xbox到
And the connect is actually the device from Xbox to
画出一个房间。
map out a room. So on those buddy
游戏,你可以做一些事情
games that you can do things
这是用过的,但你可以
with your arms. It's the one used but you can
也可以用在今天的扫描上,你可以
also use it for today's scanning and you can
只是玩好吗?
just play okay?
我有多个摄像头 正在做压倒性,但
I have multiple cameras going on overwhelming, but
我会试试的。
I'll try.
你可能在另一台摄像机上看到它的位置
Probably you can see on the other camera there where it's at
Excel在阿姆斯特丹 我有的模特
Excel at Amsterdam. The mannequin I have
以及我在这里的Kinect的设置 在它的前面,
and the setup that I have to connect here in front of it and
我们有一个惊人的。
we have an amazing.
做在实验室旋转表。
Do it in the lab rotation table.
所以,基本上用一点点
So basically with a little
绳子在那,底部是旋转的椅子。
cord there and the bottom is a rotating chair.
我们的身体可以稳定地旋转
We can rotate our body steadily enough
用于激光切割
to for the laser cut to
工作时间。
work.
所以,让我们
so let's
参见下一个
see next
有人能说点什么让我知道 我的演讲者是不是...
Can someone say something just for me to know if my speakers are
工作,因为我不得不哑巴 是的,谢谢
working because I had to mute I yes, thank
谢谢。
you.
所以我要分享我的屏幕。
So I'm gonna share my screen.
稍等。
Moment.
您可以看到 Kinect 的界面 。
For you to see the interface of the connect.
我用的是Skanect软件
So here I'm using skill net software. This
这是一个免费的版本。我认为它有一些限制,但
is a free version. I think it has some limitations but
这是您可以下载的,然后您可以使用 Kinect
it's one that you can download and then you can use the connect
自己没有Xbox。所以你不会
itself without the Xbox. So then you don't
需要Xbox来使用它。
need to have the Xbox to use it.
我把它用在Mac上 我试图在窗户上设置
I'm using it on a Mac. I try to set up on the windows that
我们在这里,但对于Windows来说,没有那么插和播放
we have here, but then for Windows is not so Plug and Play
您需要下载 Kinect 的驱动器。
you need to download the drives as well for the kinet. And then later to
功能无法工作。但我也有更旧的窗口。所以
function I couldn't have it working. But I also have older windows. So
我不知道Mac身上有什么问题
I'm not sure what was the problem there on the Mac was
直截了当的 刚刚插进Kinect上
quite straightforward. Just plugging in the connect with
在 Skanect 下载的 USB 已经
the USB downloaded in scan it and was already
认识。
recognizing.
所以,第一件事 你想在这里做
So the first thing you want to do here on the
软件只是按新的,然后你
software is just to press new and then you
重置一些 身体物体室有
have some resetting so body object room have
房间通常 Kinect 因为它是
room usually the connect as it's
用来追踪房间,效果更好
meant for tracking room. It works better
在更大的和
in bigger and
空间或者更大的物体 如果你想做一些非常详细的事情。
Spaces or bigger objects if you're trying to do something very detailed.
效果不太好,但是我们想...
It doesn't work that well, but here we want to
然后扫描身体 我们的模特儿都结束了
then scan body. So we have our mannequin over
在那里。然后它就形成了一个边框。这是它的东西。
there. So then it creates a bounding box. This is something that it
当您更改此预设设置时更改, 但是
changes as you change this preset settings, but
您也可以覆盖它,并选择更多一点。所以
you can also override it and just select a bit more. So for
举个例子,我在这里做两个二个
instance, I'm going to do here two by two
由两个。
by two.
在不同的方面工作 无线电,你可以
work in different aspects radios and you can
在那里,这是要去保存, 但我离开的一切作为
where this is going to be saved, but I leave everything as
默认和我只是
default and I just
点击开始,然后我到菜单的第二部分 这里的顶部。
press start then I go to the second part of the menu here on top.
在这里,你可以 如果你连接是正常工作。
And here you can if you're connected is working properly.
您已经可以看到一个身体图
You can already see a body figure
在顶部,否则,如果
there on the top. Otherwise, if
你什么都不说,那你需要解决一些问题
you don't say anything then there is some problem you need to
在开始之前就解决了,让我...
to solve that before starting. Let me just
看看我们的,可以推迟
see if ours. Yeah, you can delay the
从这里开始,如果你需要的话
Start by certain seconds here. If you need
还是做一些调整,或者你可以只是离开
still to do something to adjust or you can just leave to
没有什么,你可以加一个限制。
nothing and you can add a limit. This is until when it's
继续录音,然后记录你的形状。
going to keep recording and then you're going to record your shape.
因为我们有一个稳定的身体,不是
Since we have it a steady body that is not
一个人,它不会移动,但如果你这样做与某人
a person it won't move. But if you're doing this with someone
然后,这是你真正 保持静静的时刻,
then this is the moment that you really hold still and
然后按下开始,你尝试有一个中性
then you press start and you try to have a neutral
脸或者笑脸,如果你能拿着那张长长的
face or a laughing face. If you can hold that one for long and in
我们的案子,因为我们有一个旋转的桌子, 我要开始旋转
our case since we have a rotating table, I'm going to start rotating
慢慢来 另一种方式
it very slowly. Another way to
做它有一个人坐在椅子上 非常缓慢
do it is to have someone sitting on a chair and very slowly
还轮流这把椅子。
also rotating this chair.
另一种方法是旋转设备
Another way is to rotate the device
但对于Kinect,我们通常不这样做。
on the person but for The Connect usually we don't do that.
我们用感官做更多的,这是第二个,我要展示。
We do that more with the sense, which is the second one. I'm going to show.
那么我们开始吧 我要放三个
So then let's start I'm going to put just three
延迟几秒钟,我按这里的记录。
seconds delay. I press here record.
它会数起树和
It's going to count the tree and the
绿色的部分是它识别的地方,所以它是
green part is where it's recognizing. So it's
也不承认
also not recognizing the
后墙作为我的目标,我希望
the back wall as my object. I hope that as
我移动它会让回去的
I move it's gonna let go back
不错
well.
瞷眔ǐ
You do need to go right now.
它取决于 一点点的阴影,
It depends a bit on the Shadows of
我重新开始的谣言,因为
the of the rumors where I'm starting again because
我们站得太远了 墙后面。
we're standing too much of the of the wall back there.
这么说吧
So
确实是
indeed
好吧,现在,让我们来看看。
Okay now, let's see.
是啊,还是通知。
Yeah still notifications.
稍后的编辑进程。您也可以删除
Later on the edit process. You can also remove
最终
eventual
需要的对象
objects that are unwanted
我觉得像钓鱼。
I feel like fishing.
嗯,它正在输。
Well, it's losing.
何谓?
What's
还有雅各
And Jacob
被读取。
is read.
签了字,让我回到前面去
Signing in let me go back all the way to the front.
但是现在,这是非常糟糕的皮肤 展示给你的
But now this is a very bad skin showed your
整个形式不是你想要的。
whole form is not as you want.
所以,只是让你看看 如果我前进什么是即将到来
So just for you to see if I move forward what was coming
从这个皮肤。
out of this skin.
但是,你看,这不是。
But you see that it's not.
这个想法
the idea
因此,我们有一个非常模糊的物体与一个
so we have a very blurred object with a
墙后面。
wall behind.
玩一玩总是个好主意
It's always a good idea also to play a bit with the
灯光,这里有上层女神的台词
lights. So here we have some lines from the top Lady. It's their
社区或让我们看看 是否自然
Community or let's see if the natural
光线,如果它工作得更好。
light if it works a bit better.
改为:
to
说吧
you
礛琌
then you
是的,好吧,让我看看
Yes, okay. Let's see.
说
say
对,我...
yeah, I'm
将重新开始。
gonna start again.
所以,这是一个有趣的部分 生活辅导 因为我只是
So, this is a fun part of life tutorials because I just
我们开始之前就做了,现在当然了
did it before we started and then now of course
但让我们看看它是否有效,它抓住了...
it's not working. But let's see if it works. It's grabbing a
有点头,但我觉得现在更中央了
little bit of the head, but I think it's more Central now
头部更居中了，背景墙也少了一些。希望扫描顺利。
and getting less walls. Let's hope
是啊,很多积极的。
Yeah, a lot of positive.
说吧
you
是啊,它已经失去了它。
yeah, it's lost it already.
犹如虚空.
Like it's not really.
再说一遍,
so again,
等着看里面有什么,但是...
just wait to see what came out of it, but
因为我们的皮肤不好
Because we did not a good skin.
再试一次
Let's try again.
我们正在尝试一些不同的设置 不要得到墙
We are trying some different settings not to get the wall
如果有人也有小费是因为我
into it. If someone has also a tip because I
放在这。
put here.
在白色的墙上,因为 也帮助
Against the white wall because also that helps the
在它认识它之前,
contrast and before it was recognizing it
很好,不过我会再试一次
quite well, but I'll keep trying again and then
我只是继续前进 无论我们得到什么 以后
I just move forward with whatever we get and later
关于第二个备选方案的问题,以便我们
on issue on the second option so that we
不要被困在失败。
don't get stuck into failing.
但三维扫描也是这样
But that's also been how it goes with 3D scanning. Like I usually
得花点时间安排一下
have to take quite a while setting up.
他的电话
he
好吧,我换了约束箱
Okay, I change the bounding box to
一对一,所以它不是 获得背景
one to one so then it is not getting the background
现在,让我们看看这有没有用
now. So let's see if this helps a bit
对象。
object.
它已经被选为身体 但我有
It was already selected as body but I had
边框大一点,因为这个比一个大一点,然后
a bounding box a bit bigger because this is bigger than one to one but then
通过这样做,它也得到了墙
by doing so it was also getting the wall
背后,不知为什么,但现在看来
behind it. Not sure why but then now appears to
身体会变好
be getting the body better.
那你得慢慢来
Then you need to go very very slow.
后面有麻烦了 相当多影子
It's getting some trouble on the back. There's quite some Shadow. There's
没有。
no.
我安全了 拦住你
I'm safe. Stop you.
高级技术
Advanced Techniques
没有,只是得到了一些更多,
no, just got some more and
哦,是的,还有,
oh, yeah, and
差一点了
it's almost
回到我们的开始。
back to our started.
然后回到这里。
And I get back there.
我可以直接张贴。
I can just post.
所以,这一定是一个体面的。
So this must be a decent one. So
我只是暂停录制,会处理掉的
I just pause recording here. It's gonna process down
这里。
there.
那你就去重建吧 对不起
Then you oh, no, you need to go to reconstruct. Sorry.
最终完成比赛
Finalizing match then
这真的取决于它有多大
it really depends on how big it's
。如何定义此选项
watching. How also Define this
你可以花更长的时间。
you can take longer.
是的,在这里,我们还有一些
Yeah, here it is. We have some more
但我们可以清理,但我们的身体相当遥远
but we can clean that but our body is quite distant
我希望这个...
and this I hope on the
封闭网格后效果大致可以，但我们稍后还能再试。
Closing the mesh we get sort of okay back, but
我们以后可以再做一次
we could do it again later on trying to
少一点影子。
have some less shadow.
如果你要用的话
If you're using if you want to use a
非常详细的模块,你可以在这里
very detailed module, you can at this
步骤点击Fusion, 但对我们来说,它并不需要
step click on Fusion, but for us it's not needed
并需要一段时间来处理它。所以您可以稍后尝试。
and also takes a while to process it. So you can try later on when
你正在扫描,然后在这里 过程中,这是一些
you're scanning and then here in process, it's some of
用于此 3D 的进程
the of the process that you can do with this 3D
模型,所以其中一个是防水的
model. So one of them is watertight. So
你只是基本上 要关闭它作为一个
you're just basically gonna close it as one
关闭表面。
close surface.
所以现在它填满了洞
so now it's filling in the holes and
我希望这堵墙能从这里消失
And I hope this wall is going to go away just by
否则,你还需要打扫。
doing it. Otherwise, you also need to clean.
墙壁
the wall
是啊,所以现在它做了
Yeah, so now it's done
还有颜色,我的背
it also colored. My back
有点怪,不过有点怪
is a bit weird, but it's sort of
前面还不错
the front is quite
好吧,这取决于你在做什么,这也许足够好,或者你
okay and depending on what you're doing. This could be good enough or you
可能改天再运行。
could run another time.
那你还可以做一些其他的编辑
Then you can do some other edits you
可以发送它来编辑外部编辑,
can send it to edit external edit,
但你也可以听到简化的网格
but you can also hear simplify the mesh
减少可以显示的面孔数
reducing the number of faces you could
填入洞穴,对不起
fill in holes holes. Sorry,
你可以裁剪,然后这是
you can crop and then this is
一个。
one.
耕到地上,看看有没有
Crop to ground. Let's see if oh, I
应该有。
should have.
先移动
moved first
有点
it's a bit.
是啊,所以在这里通过设置
Yeah, so here by putting
你上下下都把物体沉没了
it up and down you're sinking your object into
所以,如果你想有一个非常
the ground. So if you want to have a very
直线,就我而言,有些用它。
straight base and in my case in some using that.
这个木头,我不想把它放在我身上
This this wood. I don't want it to have it on my
物体,这样我就可以把它切到那边去。
object so I can crop it over there.
看到这个有点烦人 因为命令
It is a bit annoying to see because the command
是在顶部
is on top of
你的未来
your future
也可以倾斜
and you can also tilt
有点。
it a bit.
是啊,所以我很高兴这一点。
Yeah, so I'm happy with this.
涂抹过的地面
rubbed ground
对
Yeah.
他们也可以去除零件
And they can also remove Parts
最大的模型部分的百分比要小一些
smaller in the percentage of the biggest model part this one.
我不确定,我还不知道呢
I'm not sure.
没错,它成功了。
That's yes, it worked.
你要么把颜色穿好,要么你穿好
You can either live the colors on or you
颜色可以去除,所以你可以保持你的
can remove the colors so you can just keep your
处理没有颜色的对象和此
Treat object without colors and this
已经可以出口了,所以你
would be good already to be exported. So you
可以像这样导出 。
can export it like this and on the
导出进程,您可以支持它
export process you can support it
保存为 OBJ 或 STL
and save it as an OBG or as a St L
作为
as
刚刚
just
因此,这里的运动对象, 你有不同的。
So here sport object, you have the different.
您可以支持扩展, 也可以支持不同的
extensions you can support and also the different
缩放表和
scale and
颜色和
color and
狦
if you
它在出口 我会的
And it's exporting. I will
停止分享 这样我就可以改变感官。
stop sharing so I can change to the sense.
不过,我有
But I have
我和Windows电脑没有联系
the sense in a Windows computer that I don't I'm not connected to
互联网让我无法分享屏幕。
the internet so I won't be able to share screen.
所以,它只是解释和降级 Via
So it's just explaining and demoing Via
这另一台电脑。
this other computer.
感性是这种工具.
The sense is a tool like this one.
基本是插座,所以你有一个USB
It's basically plug in play. So you have a USB
连接,你把它放在电脑上
connection. You put it on your computer and
那你需要感官软件
then you need the sense software to
运行它,但这个你也可以做
run it. But this one you can either do
它对它进行稳定编码和物体运行。
it coding it steady and object running.
像我们一样搬进月台,或者你
Moving in the platform like we did or you
也可以用这个来到处走走,它不会
can also use this one to walk around. It doesn't
有这么长的电缆,所以它不允许你走。
have such a long cable. So it doesn't allow you to go. So yeah
太疯狂了,
so wild with it,
但它运行良好 与不这么稳定
but it works well with not so steady
然后你去识别物体 当你移动,所以我
and then you go recognizing the object As you move so I'm
我会连接这台设备。
going to connect this one.
好吧,我们有一些非常高级的屏幕
Okay, we have some very Advanced screen
雪利来.
Sherry here.
前两台电脑,但这是...
first two computers, but this is the
感官软件 哦 我需要
sense software. Oops. I need
另一个老鼠。
the other Mouse.
很简单,很直观
It is quite simple and intuitive
假设我把头,我
setting I'm going to put head and I'm
试着做我物体的头 结束了
going to try just to do the head of my object which is over
在这里,你也可以做身体,因为它会
here. You could also do body because it would
更认得一点,我先别管了,小子
recognize bit more. I'll leave it boy on and then
你基本上开始扫描 这样你就不会有太多的设置
you basically start scanning so you don't have a lot of settings to
稍后再重新开始,你也可以做同样的事情,就像我们刚刚看到的接近一样
restart later on you can do the same as we just saw close
对象并做一些额外的
the object and do some extra
我开始瘦了
manipulation. So I'll start skinny,
我不知道你有没有看到我的另一只手,但是...
and I don't know if you see with my other hand, but
我指向那里,也许吧
I'm pointing it to there so probably
摆
Okay.
那么这里的挑战是 继续跟随
Then the challenge here is to keep following a
屏幕同时您必须同时显示
screen while you have to either
四处转转,但这样的话,我会试着
move around. But in this case, I'm going to try to
保持它的基地和玛丽卡。
keep it the base and Marika. My
助理会打开平台。
assistant is gonna turn the platform.
是的,你可以开始。
Yeah, you can start.
慢慢来,然后它告诉你不要动
Go slow and then it tells you to hold still when
它仍然捕捉,所以它不是说
it still capturing. So it's not saying
请继续走,然后你可以继续前进。
please go still then you can keep moving.
什麽?
What?
你停下来吗?
Do you stop?
有时有点分散注意力,然后你就得回去
Sometimes it's a little distract and then you need to go back
一点点他输了,但还是不错。
a little bit where he lost but it's still good.
你继续走。
You keep going.
对
Yeah.
然后，
and
哦,法庭结束了。
oh, it's the court finished.
这个可以更灵活地指出:
This this one gives more flexibility to point from
上面和下面,所以你真的得到
the top and the bottom and so you really get the
整个警徽,比如说,得到头发的细节。
whole badge for instance get hair details.
停下来一点。
Stop a bit.
我们会用这个穿。
We'll use this on.
摆
Okay.
你可以继续了,看看有没有回来
You can continue. Let's see if it gets back
给它。
to it.
对
Yeah.
是的,你可以离开。
Yeah, you can go.
好了,我们走 All right,
All right,
我会说总是从某个地方开始的
I would say it's always started somewhere
在这里,你就可以去
here so you can then go and
哦,错的。
Oh false.
现在,我可以用这个了
Let's now I can with this
一,你也可以暂停重启,好,对不起
one. You can also pause and restart. Okay, sorry.
但如你所说,这是好的,我们可以
But as you say that this is good and we could
结束看它是如何完成模型。
finish to see how it finished up the model.
也许你可以展示一下我的年度净身世
Maybe you can show yearly net how I was
做这些事情,所以我得到了这个
doing it with the things. So I had this
我脑子里有一根,然后我就一直握着它
one in my head and then I was just this holding it steady
而我们旋转这一个, 但你可以
and we were rotating this one, but you can
换个角度转转,如果旋转的话
also do the other way around that you rotate if you're rotating
确定那是那个圆 显示
making sure that that's that Circle that was showing
在中间 它总是指向同一个高度
in the middle. It's always pointing to the same height of
所以,这是真正的东西
your object. So this is really something that
是的,这是真正 使它保持
And yes that this is something that really makes it keep in
位置。如果你失去了轨道尝试去
place. If you lose track try to go
回到你开始的地方 或一些地点
back to where you started or some some of the spot that
你已经是真实的 所以它会再次发现,这就是
you've been already true so that it finds again and that's
基本上是这样的。
basically it.
仍在处理中.
It's still processing.
然后，
and
对
yes.
所以,当它需要很长时间 要么太好或
So when it takes long either is too good or
太遗憾了。
too bad.
那个
that
好吧,所以我们有它 像另一个,还有一些墙
okay, so we have it like the other one also some wall
在这里,但
over here, but
看起来还不错,我不是故意指的
it looks sort of okay. I was not really aimed pointing
扫描时我没有对准双手。
to the hands. So it's we
所以我们会把其余部分裁掉。
would crop it from the rest up
然后这个,你可以的
and then this one yeah you can
说吧
do.
这么说吧
so
现在的修剪,但这是一个 一种待办的梦想。
now the trim but this is a sort of a to-do dream.
然后你也可以固化你的模型。
Then you can also solidify your model.
你会得到一个封闭 砸的东西
And you would get a closed smash something that
这儿够好的了 动手吧
it's a good enough here. Do the
一样,你也可以剪下底部,然后做
same. You can also crop the bottom doing it and then you
有颜色或无颜色增加a
have also color or no color increase a
位亮度对比和做
bit brightness contrast and do
一些基本设置。
some basic settings.
然则如是喜乐.
And then if you're happy with it.
欧普
oops
结束
finish
然后你知道导出,然后
and then you know export and then
在这里,你也有这个选项 所以OBJ STL
here you have also the option so OBG STL
文件然后导出或只是
files and then you export or you just
保存此模型供稍后导出 。
saved this model to export later on.
就这样,谢谢
So that's basically it. Thank you.
我觉得有什么疑问吗?
Is there any doubts I think
更像是用这个设备
it's more also a bit of a using this devices to
也理解他们是如何工作的。
understand how they work as well.
我只要你来
I'll just you can
把摄像机转过来
turn this camera.
我不知道克劳迪娅和阿纳斯塔西亚在那里。
I don't know if Claudia or Anastasia right there. Oh you're
这里。
there.
你在说大话,我没在听
Larger are you talking I'm not listening.
亦无功用.
It's not working.
对,对。
Yes, yes.
作为工作
as work
摆
Okay.
听到了吗?
You hear me?
好的,好的,谢谢,我们来
Yep. Yep. Okay. Thank you. So here we
拥有更古老的感官版本。
have the older version of the sense.
而我只是分享从
And I'm just sharing from
因此,你只能看到接口是
that works. So you can only see the interface is
有点像一个更好的它是什么
slightly similar to the one that better it was
使用 。
using.
我们
and we
我们基本上有相同的特征,我们要去尝试
we have the same features basically and we're gonna try
来扫描此管理
to make a scan of this managing
这以前不是削减
that was previously less a cuts
并集合起来 像一周的任务是必须的。
and assembled like the assignment of the week is required.
我们要试着看看会发生什么
And we're gonna try to see what happens.
有点像
It was kind of.
所以,从屏幕上你可以看到,你有
So as you can see from the screen, you have
来决定你是否要扫描
the option to decide if you're gonna scan a
小型物体 中型物体或大型物体。
small object a medium object or a large object. We're gonna
向媒介前进。
go for the medium.
以同样的方式
and in the same way
在通过颜色缝合之前,如果
before you sew through the color you can recognize if
你太亲近了
you are too close.
或离物体太远,这是...
Or too far from the object. It's a
例如,保持45度的好做法。
good practice to keep 45 degrees. For example.
从激光到一个点 你正在尝试
From the laser towards a point you're trying
要扫描。
to scan.
如果你有一个旋转的桌子,
And also if you have a turning table,
比如说,我们用的是一家商店。
so for example, we're using a store. It's something
如果你想要保持自己的话,非常有用
very useful if you want to keep yourself
在同一个位置。
in the same position.
所以我们想做点什么
So we trying to do something really
快速不动。
quick without moving.
我们可以开始了。
And we can start.
所以按下开始。
So press the start.
当然,还有隐藏按钮之类的设置
Of course. Also, there are settings like hidden buttons
你可以调整。
that you can adjust.
例如,决议
for example the resolution
所以,你不会结束 一个真正的重网。
so you're not gonna end up with a really heavy mesh.
好,我们正式开始,我开始
Okay, we are officially starting and I'm
试图慢慢旋转。
trying to slowly rotate.
一、导 言
the table
摆
Okay.
太恶心了 我们已经失去追踪了
That's sick. We already lost tracking.
总是会快速的,也许
always going to fast Maybe
我重新开始。
I start over.
开始
start
并尝试上下移动。
also try to move up and down.
要抓住这个模型有点复杂
To catch this model is a bit complex
挑战性强,但我们以前做过,所以我们
and challenging but we have done it before so we're
确定结果可能来得及
sure that the result might come and a
不错的方式。
nice way.
如果你试图扫描例如空格 而不是尝试
If you're trying to scan for example spaces Instead try
离开。
to go.
向上移动
up
所以有时很棘手的一点是
So sometimes tricky point is to
掩蔽并关闭洞穴。
cover and to close the holes. That
可能当你从顶部来头。
might come when you come the head from Top.
我们只是展示一个小
We're just demonstrating a small
对象。到目前为止,所有的一切。你看起来
object. So so far everything. You looks
不错。
good.
当然,你花更多的时间扫描
Of course the more time you spend scanning the
对象的网格最精确的部分是尾部,但
object the more precise your mesh would be at the end, but
我觉得我们该走了
I think more or less we're good to go.
好吧,那么,让我们来看看我们得到了什么。
Okay, so, let's see what we got.
我们可以去下一个。
We can go next.
简单的按钮和我们的扫描
Just simple buttons and our scan
将会与我们一起。
will get with us.
好吧,它满是洞,但它是
Okay, it's full of holes, but it's
之前也已经考虑过了
something that's also wait so previously into account and
我们可以试试看
we can just try to see
与
with the
基本选项如固化。例如,什么样的效果。
basic options like solidify. For example, what kind of effect.
为了把机器关到
With that in order to close the machine to
一个固体。
a solid.
因此,这样我们就可以得到一个STL和一个
So this way we will get an STL and an
如果我们想保持 纹理和
obj if we want to keep the texture and the
材料的颜色。
color of the materials.
应该准备好了。
Should be ready.
摆
Okay.
这不关你的事
This is not about right.
当然你也可以 如果你发现任何
And of course you can also if you spot any
更多的话,但这应该是
more words, but this should be should be
几乎一个紧水的固体,所以你
a pretty much a watertight solid so you
能够实际开始导出此选项
can actually start exporting this
网格和玩弄其他软件
mesh and play around with another software for
示例网格混音器。
example mesh mixer.
犀牛聚变等
Rhino fusion and so on so
接下来你就可以了。
you can just do next.
保存
and Save
以目前为例,
as still for example of obj in
如我们所说 如果你想保持颜色和纹理
case as we said if you want to keep the colors and the textures.
现在我们有了另一个西班牙人
now we have another Spanish
我们想
we want to
显示
to show
你可以在这里停止截图。
you can stop screenshot in here.
我们能得到
and we can get
已连接
connected
и琌
I'm just
来展示一下
going to show just
好吧,那么在试图使用的地方
okay. So where trying to use
Artec 扫描仪？
the Arctic?
职业战略折扣
It's a professional strategy discount
这里。
there.
使用与感知相同的技术
That uses the same technology as the sense this
结构是这样的,所以它要去 投射出来
structured like so it's going to project them up
光线。
of light.
这一点应该如此。
This should be connected so.
扫描仪这个,我们想让你显示。
The scanner this and we want you to show.
今天早上我们做的非常令人惊叹
A really stunning we did this morning.
现在你可以了
Now you can
见屏幕.
see the screen.
所以,如果你想 比较这个可以
So if you want to compare this can
和我们之前见过的一样
with the one we saw before.
这个比较专业
This one is more professional.
这个课程你可以从3D模型本身中发现.
This course you can spot from the 3D model itself.
所以在这里,我们设法得到了所有
So here we managed to got all
这些细节。
these details.
我知道,我记得。
I know.
从物理物体上可以看到3个.
You can see three from the physical objects.
连标签
and even the label
以肥皂为单位
of the soap
这是专业的扫描仪 比如说
This is a professional scanner for for example
保健应用
Healthcare applications Orthopedics City
辅助科技.
assistive Technologies.
通常你不会在实验室里找到这个 而是为了那些东西
Usually you're not find this in the lab, but for the things
你扫描的东西 类似感官是
that you are scanning something like sense is
瞒秨 Τ届
very good to separate. It works
类似的方式,但您可以看到界面
in a similar way, but as you can see the interface of the
这里的软件您还有许多要玩的设置。
software here you have many more settings to play with.
所以,举例来说,如果你想
So for example, if you want to
尝试演示,实际上去
try a demo and actually went to
给你看
show you
嗯,这个工作流程
um the workflow of this
例如这里
so for example here
这是你在这里看到的结果
This is the result that you are showing seeing here
不同种类的天空,我们可以分开做。
of different kind of Skies that we can do separately. So
一切都没有记录下来,
everything is not recorded and
全部扫描一次,但步数不同
scanned all at once but in different steps
因此,你可以决定 例如扫描顶部
so you can decide for example to scan the top
编。
part.
本身还是正面还是侧面?
Itself or the front or the side?
在这里,你看到了
and here you see
以表面为例,
the amount for example of surfaces that
被称作
were called that
大约 500［原文不清，需对照视频复核］。
something like 500 recession
这样你就可以继续了。
so you can resume.
每当你需要时,你可以暂停
And you can pause every time you need to get
您的 3D 对象的最佳网站 。
the best site of your 3D object.
到最后,你可以运行
And at the end you can run the
自动驾驶,你可以告诉,你可以问这个软件。
autopilot you can tell and you can ask this software.
这一切合起来太过分了
Too much all this coming together into an
对象。当然还有其他工具可以修正
object. And of course there are other tools to fix
孔以加于清净.
holes to add it to clean.
这些都是非常复杂的网状网状,例如,让我
These are very complex mesh. For example, let me
需要一段时间来扫描。
take a while to scan. So also in terms of for example
它会比它重得多
of the sides. It will be much heavier than
曾经如此的一次
one so before
我想我们可以试试
I think we can just try to
停止屏幕共享 。
stop screen share.
做点什么吧
and do something like
礛
and so then
你知道吗?
You know.
刚刚
just
所以,还好。
So, okay.
所以我们可以做一个新的。
So we can make a new one.
总是好的东西
What's something always good
记住,就是尝试
to keep in mind is to try
以扫描不反射的对象
to scan objects not reflective
或者像瓶子一样透明
or transparent like for example bottles.
以防这个空间有点挑战性,因为它真的
In case this space is a bit challenging because it's really
闪亮的白色 所以其实有点
shiny white. So it's actually a bit
反射。 反射。
reflective.
但对于这个扫描仪来说是件好事
But for this scanner was was a good
演示。
demonstration.
是的,我们可以试着扫描 相同的模特儿。
Yeah, we can try to scan the same mannequin.
而过程也是一样的。
And the process is the same.
是的,我们可以开始 仅仅展示一个
Yeah, we can start just to demonstrate a
位数。
bit.
何时
when
当然,它扫描了一个物体。
It's of course and it scans an object. Of course
例如,这里的分辨率是0.05毫米。
the resolution here for example is something like 0.05 millimeters.
所以有时候也非常狡猾
So sometimes is also very tricky
保持稳定,保持同一位置。
to be stable and to keep the same position.
也有温度等特征.
There are also features like the temperature.
扫描仪
scanner
你可以说照片每秒。
and you can say that the photographs per second.
速度比这要快得多
The speed of it is much faster compared to
之前的恩爱。
the previous kindness.
举个例子,我们可以抓住一面,我们可以
Okay. So for example, we can catch one side and we can
别闹了
stop it.
而且,这场比赛真的很困难。
Also, this match is really hard.
举个例子 开始吧
What we can just show for example and start.
我们上周做的另一次扫描是
Another scanning we did last week that was
这个圣母安德烈
this Makita Andre.
这是三维模型的结果
And this is the result of the 3D model in the
计算机的3D查看器。这就是对象。
3D viewer of the computer. So this is the object.
物理的,同时你可以看到,
The physical and at the same time you can see that the
相同的纹理按钮。
same amount of textures buttons.
和一些细节
and little details
亦有记载.
There's been also recorded.
这里的物理模型和数字模型
here in the physical and the Digital model
花了多长时间?
How long did it take?
20分钟
20 minutes
是啊,当然,这是STL,但是,
yeah, and also of course, this is the STL but
狦Τ you
If you have the obj you
将查找所有标志或标签
will spot all the logos or the labels all the
按钮和不同颜色。
buttons and the colors of different.
好吧,我想就这样了。
Okay, I guess that's all.
我不知道你有没有问题
I don't know if you have questions.
或 时 间
or
好奇心,我们可以
Curiosities we can
是啊,我们刚刚结束。
Yeah, we just ended.
我不知道在别人中是否有疑问或
I don't know if in anybody else questions or
好奇心我们可以回答。
Curiosities we can answer.
有时候用电脑和电脑很困难
Sometimes it's very tricky to use to computers and to
同时向实验室里的人展示
show at the same time to the people in the lab with the
学生的一切,这就是发生。
students everything. That's that's happening.
好吧,我觉得。
Okay, I think.
吾等今为好.
We're good for today.
对,棒极了
Yes, awesome.
所以,如果你没有
So if if you don't have
扫描仪和确保
a scanner and make sure
可以下载不同的应用程序
that you can download different applications on
电话和高度
the phone and also highly
鼓励您尝试摄影
encourage you to try photography with
照片上的照片,这真的有用
the pictures with the photos. That's really working.
这一切都非常有力。
It is all very very robust.
这么说吧,科技就是如此
Let's say technology so
你也可以试试看。
you can also try that.
是啊,你发现很多 已经和我们
Yeah, and you find a lot of already and our
网站和典型的五种不同资源
website and a classic five different resources in terms
某些网站,您可以查看和测试。
of some website that you can check and try out.
好的,谢谢大家
Okay. Thank you everyone.